{
    "id": "996aa72d71964451aeb3e099d1c7294f",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I think you .................................. consult a doctor.",
            "description": "The expression I think you should is used to make polite suggestions.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "need"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Let's buy some flowers for her, .....................................?",
            "description": "Shall is used in question tags after let. ",
            "answers": [
                "should we",
                "will we",
                "shall we"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't mind .................................... the housework.",
            "description": "We use an ing form after I don't mind.",
            "answers": [
                "to do",
                "doing",
                "to doing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't like ........................................... up early in the morning.",
            "description": "Like is followed by an infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "getting",
                "to get",
                "to getting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................ I get you something to drink?",
            "description": "Shall I is used in polite offers to do something.",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................. you like me to type your letters for you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should",
                "Shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I want you ......................................... this report my evening.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to finish",
                "finishing",
                "to finishing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind if I ...................................... some music?",
            "description": "We use a past tense after would you mind...?",
            "answers": [
                "play",
                "played",
                "had played"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I'm not really into films. I would rather ..................................... a book.",
            "description": "Would rather is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "to read",
                "reading"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We ............................................. each other in a long time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "haven't seen",
                "didn't see",
                "don't see"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "John ..................................... ten minutes ago.",
            "description": "We use the past simple to say when something happened. ",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "has left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We were having lunch when someone ......................................... on the floor.",
            "description": "The past simple is used to talk about the short action that happened in the middle of the long action. ",
            "answers": [
                "knocked",
                "has knocked",
                "was knocking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}